The struggle. The striving. The sweat. The hopes. The heartbreaks.
American Anthem is a romance film directed by Albert Magnoli.
Steve is a talented gymnast who has given up competition
and is working at his father's bike shop.
Julie is the new girl at his old gym, who has moved to
town to train with their powerful coach.
Inspired by Julie, Steve resumes training.
While dealing with the conflicts in their personal lives and the stress
of training, they prepare for the US Olympic Trials.
Steve Tevere, played by Mitch Gaylord.
Julie Lloyd, played by Janet Jones.
Coach Soranhoff, played by Michael Pataki.
Becky Cameron, played by Maria Anz.
Kirk Baker, played by Stacy Maloney.
Mr. Tevere, played by John Aprea.
American Anthem is a 1986 American sports drama film directed by
Albert Magnoli, starring Mitch Gaylord and Janet Jones.
The film was produced by Lorimar Motion Pictures and
released in North America by Columbia Pictures.
Gaylord was a member of the gold medal-winning U.S.
men's gymnastics team at the 1984 Summer Olympics.
The tone is emotional.